Tufts University Faculty Annual UP140
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Faculty Annual
1940 -- 1983
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Vice Provost
UP140
0.75 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains annual issues of "Faculty Annual" from 1940 to 1983 which provides details of current areas of research and scholarly interest as well as publications of University Faculty. Originally published in 1909-10 as part of the president's annual report to the Trustees. Between 1938 and 1956 it was published annually as "Faculty Publications: A Bibliography of Books, Articles, Monographs published by members of the several faculties."
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Vice Provost was formerly known as the Office of the Associate Provost for Research. Between November 1984 and July 1986 the positions of Director of Government Resources, Health Sciences, and the Director of Government Resources, Arts and Sciences, were moved from the University Development office to the Office of the Senior Vice President and Provost with the creation of the positions of Associate Provost for Research, Boston Campus and the Associate Provost for Research, Medford Campus. The two positions were combined during the 1993-1994 academic year, and the position was also expanded to include the Grafton campus. In 2004, the Associate Provost for Research became the Vice Provost.
- Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1940 -- 1983; 1940 -- 1968; UP140.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of "Faculty Annual" which provides details of current areas of research and scholarly interest as well as publications of University Faculty. Originally published in 1909-1910 as part of the president's annual report to the Trustees. Between 1938 and 1956 it was published annually as "Faculty Publications: A Bibliography of Books, Articles, Monographs published by members of the several faculties"
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1940-06; UP140.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1941-04; UP140.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1942-04; UP140.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1943-04; UP140.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1944-04; UP140.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1945-04; UP140.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1946-04; UP140.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1947-04; UP140.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1948-04; UP140.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1949-06; UP140.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1950-06; UP140.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1951-06; UP140.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1952-06; UP140.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Faculty Publications, 1953-06; UP140.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Publications, 1954-06; UP140.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Publications, 1956-06; UP140.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Publications, 1957-06; UP140.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1958-06; UP140.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1959-06; UP140.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1960-06; UP140.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1961-06; UP140.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1962-06; UP140.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual3, 1963-06; UP140.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1964-06; UP140.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1965-06; UP140.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1966-06; UP140.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1967-06; UP140.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1968-06; UP140.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1981-04; UP140.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Tufts University Faculty Annual, 1983-04; UP140.001.002.00002 (Box 2)